<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Agro Nutritions</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Test</string>
    <string name="api_key">hg%$g5467GFT6^YTRGjj</string>
    <string name="Rs">\u20B9</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <!--<string name="prompt_signup">Don\'t have an account? <u>Sign Up</u></string>-->
    <string name="prompt_signup">Don\'t have an account?\n<u>Join Now</u></string>
    <string name="copyright">Powered by Agro Nutritions. &#169; 2020</string>
    <string name="delivery_time">Order timing 08:00 AM  to  07:00 PM</string>
    <string name="logout">logout</string>
    <string name="add_cart">Add cart</string>
    <string name="login_sign_up_to_avail_our_services">Login/Join Now to avail our services</string>
    <string name="join_now">Join Now</string>
    <string name="join_new">New</string>
    <string name="join_login">Login</string>
    <string name="join_login2"><u>Login</u></string>
    <string name="terms">1. SINCE AGRO NUTRITIONS IS A SOLE PROPRIETORSHIP FIRM, COMMISSION AGENTS HAVE NO AUTHORITY TO CLAIM TO BE EMPLOYEES OF THE FIRM.\n


2.THE EACH MEMBER THE FIRM WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE ACCOUNT THAT GIVEN BY THE TIME OF REGISTRATION OF THERE IDENTITY, WITHIN THREE TO SEVEN DAYS AFTER THE COMPLETION OF THERE TARGET.\n


3.SINCE A HUGE AMOUNT HAS TO BE TRANSFERRED,THE RECIPIENT HAS PAY THE TAXES HIM SELF.\n


4.IT MAY TAKE FOUR TO FOURTEEN DAYS FOR THE ORDERD ITEMS TO ARRIVE BY COURIER.\n


5.ALTHOUGH AGRO NUTRITIONS PRODUCT HAVE BEEN TESTE IN INDIA .THE EFFECT OF CLIMATE CHANGE ON THE SOIL OF THE RESERVOIR MAY BE LESS IN THE RESULT.\n


6.THOSE WHO INTEND TO RETURN THE ITEM MUST RETURN THE ITEM TO THE FIRM WITHIN SEVEN DAYS PRIOR TO PURCHASE,THE SAME FORM IN WHICH THE ITEM WAS RECEIVED.THE BALANCE AFTER THE COURIER CHARGE WILL BE REFUNDED TO THE CUSTOMERS ACCOUNT WITH IN ONE MONTH.\n


7.COMPLAINTS AND LITIGATION AGAINST THIS ENTERPRISE WILL BE UNDER THE JURISDICTION OF THE BANGALORE JUDICIARY ONLY.\n


8.FIRM IS SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR PROVIDING PRODUCTS AND PAYING APPROPRIATE COMMISSIONS TO ENTREPRENEURS RANKING FROM EXICUTIVE TO SENIOR MANAGER.\n


9.EVERY ONE FROM THE EXICUTIVE ONWARDS HAS NO RIGHT OR AUTHORITY BEYOND THE FIXED PERCENTAGE COMMISSION ON THE GOODS SOLD THROUGH THEM.THE SENIOR MANAGER ABOVE HAS THE AUTHORITY TO USE ALL THE CORRESPONDENCE IN THIS PROJECT ONLY FOR THOSE ABOVE AND FIRM OWNER.\n


10.ALL TRANSACTIONS ARE DONE WITH THE IDENTY OF THE COMMISSION AGENTS ,SO ALL TRANSACTIONS IDENTY IS MANDATORY.\n


11.THE FIRM WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY MISUSE OF BOOKED PRODUCTS FOR NON DELIVERY OR NON RETURN OF GOODS DUE TO UNFORESEEN REASONS SUCH AS WEATHER ,STRIKE.\n


12.FIRM HAS NO OBLIGATION TO PROMOTE COMMISSION AGENTS OTHER THAN THE OCCASIONAL ADVERTICEMENT FOR THE SALE OF GOODS.\n


13,NO COMMISSION AGENT HAS THE POWER TO REDUCE THE PRICE OF GOODS INORDER TO INCREASE SALES FIRM HAS THE POWER TO CANSEL THEIR IDENTY WITH OUT WARNING IF SUCH ALLEGATIONS ARE NOTICED.\n


14.THE FIRM HAS FULL AUTHORITY TO CANCEL THE IDENTY OF THOSE WHO ARE ABUSING THE PRODUCTS OF THIS FIRM.\n


15.ONLY FIRM HAS THE POWER TO MAKE PERIODIC CHANGES TO PRODUCTS AND MARKETS.\n


16.THOSE WHO MARKET IN A MANNER OTHER THAN THOSE PRESCRIBED BY THE FIRM SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY TO THE FIRM IN THEIR PRODUCTS.\n


17.SINCE ALL THE ACTIVITIES OF THE INSTITUTION ARE DONE THROUGH CASH,NO CHECK OR DEMAND DRAFT IS ACCEPTED HERE.\n


18.WE RELY ON COURIOR SERVICES FOR DELIVERY OF THE GOODS .SO FIRM WILL NOTIFY THE CUSTEMER VIA S M S WHEN THE DELIVERY IS SOUGHT, AND THE ENTERPRISE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR THE RETURN OF THE BOOKD GOODS WITH OUT RECEIVING.\n


19.GOODS CAN BE BOOKED FROM COUNTRIES OUT SIDE INDIA BUT DELIVERY CAN ONLY BE MADE TO INDIA.</string>


</resources>